Disgusting. This place still smells like piss and crap.
真噁心，這裡還是一樣充滿屎尿味
Shall I take your jacket?
要我幫你拿外套嗎？
What have you done?
你做了什麼？
Because you stole the forbidden book...
都是因為你偷了禁書…
-That's because you... -Shut up.
–那是因為你… –閉嘴
Hey, why is he here?
喂，這傢伙怎麼會在這裡？
He's one of us now.
他是我們的新夥伴
Store it here for now.
這東西先放在這裡吧
Don't you have to return it to the Five Spears?
你不用拿去還給五矛會嗎？
This is the most secure place.
放在這裡是最安全的
Because you...
都是因為你…
By the way, have you taken care of that Yokai? What's taking so long?
話說回來，你處理掉那個妖怪了嗎？ 怎麼拖這麼久？
Leave it to me.
交給我吧
The police are snooping around now. They're looking for him, too.
警察開始四處查案了 他們也在找這傢伙的下落
Failures are unacceptable.
不可以再失敗了
It's all part of the plan.
一切都按照計畫進行
The plan?
計畫？
This is the plan!
就是這個計畫！
I don't have time for this.
我沒時間陪你們玩這套
Anyway, just get rid of that Yokai.
總之，趕快解決那個妖怪吧
Can I eat his brain?
我可以吃掉他的腦嗎？
Our plan takes priority.
先執行計畫
Izzy?
伊姬？
Good morning.
早安
It's a success.
看來成功了
Izzy, what's this?
伊姬，這是什麼？
It's more secure now.
我設下了一些防備
Can you let me down?
可以放我下來嗎？
Blood is rushing to my head.
我要腦充血了
This is something else.
這裡好像變得…滿厲害的
To find the remaining four heads,
為了找到剩下的四顆頭
I need this Dragon's Magatama.
我需要這塊龍勾玉
What is that?
那是什麼？
This magatama has the power to identify
這塊勾玉的力量能夠指認出
the Guardians of the seal that trap us Yokai.
那些困住我們妖怪的結界守護者
I checked for the magatama's location. It's here.
我調查了勾玉的位置，就在這裡
Wait. That's the exhibition room at my university.
等等，這是我學校的展覽室
Is that true?
真的嗎？
What is it doing there?
學校怎麼會有這種東西？
Take me there.
帶我去那裡
Hey, what do you plan to do once you find that magatama?
那麼，找到勾玉後妳打算做什麼？
I'll find the Guardians and collect the remaining heads.
我會找出守護者，收集剩下的頭顱
That's not good. Can't you talk it over?
這樣不行，不能用對談解決問題嗎？
There you go again.
你又來了
Times are different now.
時代不同了
I get that these Guardians' ancestors are your enemies,
我明白這些守護者的祖先是妳的敵人
and you detest them,
妳很憎恨他們
but if my great-great grandfather did something bad, would you kill me?
但如果我的曾曾祖父 做了壞事，妳會殺了我嗎？
With no hesitation.
我會毫不猶豫殺了你
-I can't help you. -Why not?
–我不能幫妳 –為什麼？
You'd help your friends, but not me?
你會幫助朋友，卻不幫助我？
I don't want you to kill anybody.
我不希望妳殺人
This is pointless.
真是白費唇舌
Wait, Izzy!
等等，伊姬
You won't help me.
你又不會幫我
No. There must be another way.
不，一定還有其他的辦法
-Like another spell. -It doesn't exist.
–例如尋找別的咒語… –沒有這種東西
I've had enough of this. I'll go alone.
夠了，我自己一個人去
Wait!
等等！
Rule number three. Don't kill anyone.
別忘了我們的第三條規則，不要殺人
OFFERING TO THE GODS
供品
IPPONGI CONSTRUCTION COMPANY
一本木建設
Sakon Renjo. He's a legal advisor for Ippongi Construction,
連城左近，除了擔任 一本木建設的顧問律師之外
and has other extensive clientele.
手上似乎還有許多客戶
WITNESS, SAKON RENJO
證人，連城左近
He also handles Mikurube Shipping and Yomoda Brewery.
他服務的對象還包括 三廻部海運和四方田酒造
These are huge corporations. It's kind of annoying.
全都是大公司，有點討厭
Would you like one?
要吃嗎？
Do you prefer Chocorooms?
你比較喜歡蘑菇山巧克力？
By the way, what's with that baseball mitt?
話說回來，怎麼會有那個棒球手套？
I thought I might play catch with my son. It's been awhile.
很久沒陪兒子 玩丟接球了，想說來玩一下
Your son is a university student, right?
警部的兒子是大學生吧？
It's not weird at all.
不，這一點也不會奇怪
You two are close.
你們感情真好
It's the opposite.
剛好相反
I grew up without a father.
我的成長過程中沒有父親陪伴
It's hard for me to get close to my son.
所以不太知道怎麼跟兒子拉近距離
He'll see that you want to do something together.
你想跟他一起做些什麼 這份心意他會明白的
I mean, my family wasn't that close, either,
我跟家人也沒那麼親密
but we all followed Madam Yoshiko's oracle.
但我們全家都遵從芳子夫人的神諭
Madam Yoshiko?
芳子夫人？
Don't you know the charismatic fortune-teller?
你不知道嗎？她是教主級的命理師
Our subject.
對象現身了
Are you sure that using this personal computer thing
你確定用這個叫做電腦的東西
is more reliable than using a spell?
比咒語更有效嗎？
It's faster online.
網路比較快速
And it's more wicked!
而且更加邪惡！
I thought you'd be back.
我就知道你會回來
I just wanted a quiet place to think.
我想找個安靜的地方想事情
This is a special place.
這個地方很特別
Actually, what you said has been on my mind this whole time.
其實我一直在思考住持你上次說的話
It's about the special powers.
關於神秘力量的那件事
Yes, powers are constantly around us,
是的，力量就像愛與性
just like love and sex.
始終在我們的身邊
I believe in special powers.
我相信有神秘力量的存在
But it's so absurd...
但一切實在太不合理…
I don't entirely understand. Google and books were no help.
我無法完全理解 上網搜尋或翻書也查不到
I don't know what to do.
我不知道該怎麼辦
There's a limit to what we can learn from books and the Internet.
能從書和網路上學到的東西有限
There's only one thing I want to say.
我想說的只有一件事
Power is something that's constantly changing.
力量會不斷變化
On the contrary, the world
反之，也能透過這個世界
is able to change the power.
來改變力量
Let's say you're caught in a cursed bond.
假如陷入了被詛咒的羈絆
Is it possible to change that?
這是有可能改變的嗎？
Yes.
是的
However, empathy with one another is necessary to change that bond.
然而，如果要改變這份羈絆 就必須同理對方的處境
You look at things from the other person's perspective.
先站在對方的立場看事情
How can you change the way things are?
再去思考怎樣才能改變這件事
Think about that.
你好好想想吧
HEADQUARTERS FOR THE ERADICATION OF ORGANIZED CRIME GROUPS
六畔警察局
This is a report on Sakon's actions.
以下是左近這幾天的行動
He had breakfast with the CEO of Mikurube Shipping.
早上在魚市場 與三迴部海運的社長共進早餐
Then he went to work at Ippongi Construction.
然後去一本木建設上班
Midday, he visited Yomoda Sake Brewery, then to Ippongi Construction.
中午去拜訪四方田酒造 接著回到一本木建設
At night, he stopped by Nijoji Temple and went home.
晚上他去了二淨寺之後就返回住處
It's the same every day. It's Sakon's routine.
每天行程都一樣，這就是左近的日常
He seems like a hard-working attorney.
感覺只是一位勤奮的律師
Oh, but last night, the investigator reported
但是昨晚尾隨他的搜查員報告說
that he couldn't confirm Sakon leaving the temple.
他沒看到左近離開寺廟
What does that mean?
這是怎麼回事？
Who knows? Maybe a waterfall training.
天曉得，可能在瀑布下修行吧
Waterfall training?
瀑布修行？
What are you saying?
妳在說什麼？
YOMODA SAKE BREWERY
四方田酒造
MIKURUBE SHIPPING COMPANY
三迴部海運
NIJOJI TEMPLE
二淨寺
Mitsuki? Mitsuki.
光希…
Are you here? Mitsuki...
你在這裡嗎？光希…
Where did she go?
牠跑去哪裡了？
Mitsuki!
光希！
Mitsuki?
光希？
Mitsuki.
光希
Ms. Sawada.
澤田大人
-Mitsuki? -Yes, it's me.
–光希？ –是的，是我
You're talking!
你會講話？
I am your cat.
我是妳養的貓
Your ancient folklore knowledge is excellent.
妳擁有卓越的古代民俗知識
That's why I decided to reveal my true self to you.
所以我決定讓妳看看我真正的樣貌
Are you really Mitsuki?
你真的是光希嗎？
I am, meow.
是我啊，喵
I need your help, meow.
我需要妳的幫忙，喵
Where is the Dragon's Magatama, meow?
龍勾玉在哪裡，喵？
I wanted to ask you something, too.
我也想問你一件事
Do you like the food I always give you?
你喜歡我平常給你吃的食物嗎？
What do you like? Canned food or dry food?
你喜歡吃罐頭還是乾飼料？
Stupid.
真無聊
I'll ask again. Where's the Dragon's Magatama?
就問妳，龍勾玉放在哪裡？
Are you really Mitsuki?
你真的是光希嗎？
Where is the Dragon's Magatama?
龍勾玉在哪裡？
Who are you?
妳是誰？
Answer me!
回答我！
That magatama was loaned to us for an exhibit from an anonymous owner.
那塊勾玉是 一位匿名藏家借給我們展覽的
It's been returned already!
已經還給人家了！
I don't know where it is now.
我不知道東西在哪裡
Could it be... A Yokai?
難道妳是…妖怪？
Does they really exist?
妖怪真的存在嗎？
You good-for-nothing!
妳這個沒用的東西！
I'll show you a real Yokai.
我就讓妳見識一下真正的妖怪
You scared me. Don't do that.
妳嚇到我了，別這樣
-Hachi, help me. -What?
–小八，幫我個忙 –什麼？
The magatama was moved. I need to locate it.
勾玉被移動了，我需要找到它的位置
ANCIENT MAGIC EXHIBITION
古代咒術展
"Anonymous." If the owner is anonymous,
“匿名人士”啊 既然藏家是匿名人士
it might be hard to track it unless we hack into the school's server.
除非駭入學校的伺服器 否則可能很難追蹤勾玉的下落
Do that "hack" thing, then.
那就來做“駭入”那件事吧
You can't hack that easily!
要駭入可沒那麼簡單
I kept your promise and didn't kill anyone.
我可是有聽你的話，沒殺死任何人呢
It would have been so much easier to kill.
比起來，殺人容易多了
You followed the rule.
妳遵守了規則
What's so funny?
有什麼好笑的？
Nothing.
沒事
Oh! I know someone who's good at hacking!
對了，我有認識 一個擅長駭入伺服器的人
Listen up!
聽好了！
The greatest competition in e-sports, E LEGENDS,
電競界最盛大的比賽，電競傳奇盃賽
is being held at our home.
今年要在我們的主場舉行
It's a great opportunity.
機會千載難逢
Let's utilize this to get our first win.
我們要利用主場優勢贏得首次勝利
That's when... You're late!
到時候…你遲到了！
Who is she?
她是誰？
This is Izzy. She's my girlfriend.
她是伊姬，是我的女朋友
She's no balding old man.
居然不是禿頭大叔
Blink twice if you didn't come of your own free will.
如果妳不是自願來的就眨眼兩次
Is it okay to kill him?
我可以殺了他嗎？
Yes.
可以
No! Don't!
不！不行！
Hey, Hachi!
喂，小八！
You are breaking the rules of Team Under Dogs.
你違反了我們敗犬隊的規則
You have rules here, too?
這裡也有規則嗎？
People like rules.
人類很喜歡規則
Don't forget the team rule. The team takes priority at all times!
別忘了團隊的規則 永遠要優先考量團隊
Sex is prohibited. Maintain your energy as a man.
禁止性行為，保存男人的能量
We are boxers in a gaming world.
我們是遊戲界的拳擊手
Terauchi, we don't need that explanation.
寺內，不需要這種說明
You know they aren't in a relationship...
想也知道他們不是那種關係…
Hachi, why did you bring a girlfriend to this sacred place?
小八，你怎麼帶女朋友 來這個神聖的地方？
We came to see Ms. Hikari.
我們是來見小光大人的
Who, me?
什麼，找我？
We need your help with something.
我們需要妳的幫忙
-Izzy, nice to meet you. -Nice to meet you.
–伊姬，很高興認識妳 –很高興認識妳
I'm not here. I don't know anything.
我不在這裡，我什麼都不知道
Whatever. Focus.
好了，專心練習吧
I'll allow you to watch today.
今天我就允許妳來參觀
But do not interfere from now on.
但從現在起，不要干擾大家
No distracting cosplay costumes, either.
也不要穿這種 令人分散注意力的角色扮演服裝
-This is anaconda... -No talking!
–這是用蟒蛇… –不准閒聊！
Awesome!
超讚的！
Hey, where did you buy it?
那副隱形眼鏡在哪買的？
Focus! We'll start the match.
專心一點！要開始比賽了
Hachi!
小八！
Wait here.
妳在這裡等一下
Let's go forward.
繼續前進…
Oh, they're coming from the back.
敵人追來了
Go! Let's go!
上吧！我們上！
-Hachi, handle it. -Okay, count on it.
–小八，你能瞄準他嗎？ –好，交給我
-Okay, nice. -I'll aim for the foot.
–好，很棒 –我對準腳部攻擊
-Hikari, heal us! -You got it.
–小光，幫忙回血！ –沒問題
Show boobs, or get lost
露出胸部，否則就滾開
Hikari? Healing! Healing!
小光？回血…
-I'm sorry. Hold on. -Healing!
–對不起，怎麼回事？等等 –快點治療！
Women can't play games
女人從以前就不會玩遊戲
-Die! -Hey!
–去死吧！ –喂！
I'm not talking to you! There's a troll on the field.
我不是在跟你說話！ 戰場上有人找碴
Cut the crap! You shit.
開什麼玩笑，混帳！
What the hell?
這是怎樣？
What is this?
怎麼回事？
I don't know, but I suddenly got a chat degrading woman. What is this?
不知道，突然有人傳來 貶低女性的內容，到底是怎樣？
-Didn't you turn it off? -I did!
–妳沒關掉聊天嗎？ –我有啊！
You probably offended someone.
妳一定惹到了誰
You used femininity to earn.
畢竟妳用美色賺錢
Hey, you went too far! Apologize to Hikari.
喂，你這話太過分了！向小光道歉
My bad. I went too far.
對不起，我太過分了
Our API is hacked.
有人駭進了遊戲的API
All the servers are locked.
伺服器都鎖住了
-What? -Let me see.
–什麼？ –讓我看
What the hell is this?
這是什麼鬼？
Those are weird.
這是什麼奇怪的文字？
Sanskrit characters. What does it say?
是梵文，不曉得是什麼意思
It's a trap.
這是陷阱
Do you get it?
妳看得懂？
"Seek me out if you want it back."
“想要回伺服器，就來找我”
I see.
好喔
They got some guts challenging me to a hacking contest.
竟然敢挑戰我進行駭客對決，真有種
I'll locate and kill them!
我會找出他們的位置並宰了他們！
I'll help you.
我幫妳
Shall I flay them and remove their guts?
要不要剝掉他們的皮 挖出他們的內臟？
That's super hardcore!
超猛的，讚死了！
I like you!
我欣賞妳！
Starting today,
從今天起
you are our team cheerleader!
妳就是我們敗犬隊的啦啦隊！
I located it!
找到對方的位置了！
They're at this university's library.
在這所大學的圖書館裡
Yeah!
好！
Now you know! Go get them, everyone!
既然知道位置，就快去找他們算帳吧
The coordinates are in here.
座標顯示是在這裡面
Now, who did it?
好了，犯人到底是誰？
We'll just go threatening everyone one by one.
一一威脅所有人，就能找出來了
What's going on here?
現在到底是怎樣？
We planned to return her to her original world,
我們原本是要讓她回到原本的世界
but you're helping her out now.
她卻不知不覺融入了我們？
You're seriously in deep shit.
你真的太深陷其中了
How far is this story going to go?
這件事到底還要發展到什麼程度？
I seriously can't handle it anymore.
我真的已經受夠了
Are you interfering again?
你又要來干擾我們嗎？
Tanuki is just nervous.
狸貓只是緊張而已
Nervous?
緊張？
Why? Are you scheming something again?
為什麼？你又在打什麼主意？
No! He's not used to girls.
不是啦！他只是不習慣跟女生相處
Calm down.
冷靜一點
Stop that.
別這樣
You may have a girl, but don't think your social status is higher.
別以為你交了女友 社會地位就提升了
I might have it!
我好像找到他們了
I followed the IP address. It's coming from the basement.
我追蹤了IP位址，來源在地下室
This way.
往這邊
Inukai.
犬飼同學
Hello.
妳好
-More research? -Oh, well...
–今天也來做研究嗎？ –這…
We're eagerly continuing our research about that ritual.
上次那個儀式，我們在持續研究
A ritual?
儀式？
Could you tell us about that ritual again sometime?
下次能再跟我們解釋那個儀式嗎？
What is it about?
你們在說什麼？
It's nothing.
沒事
Izzy, let me introduce you to her. This is Arisa. She's my girlfriend.
伊姬，我介紹一下 這位是有紗，她是我的女朋友
Hello.
妳好
That's a wonderful retro outfit.
這套復古服裝好棒
She's a cosplayer.
角色扮演是她的嗜好
I'm very curious about Inukai's girlfriend.
我對犬飼同學的女友很感興趣
I'm sorry. You have such beautiful hair.
抱歉，我只是覺得妳的頭髮很漂亮
Your hair looks like it would make a great brush.
妳的頭髮也是 應該能做成很棒的毛筆
What?
什麼？
Arisa, we're in a rush. We'll see you later!
有紗，我們在趕時間 那就先告辭了，回頭見
Is anybody here?
有人在嗎？
This way.
往這邊
What? It's a dead end.
什麼？這不是死胡同嗎？
But it looks like it's ahead of here.
但位置看起來是要再往前走
Look at that symbol!
你們看那個符號
-What? Cut the crap! -Hold it.
–什麼？開什麼玩笑 –等等
-Wow. -This is no joke.
超猛的
What is this place?
這是什麼地方？
Is it okay to come in here?
進來這裡好嗎？
This is truly horrific.
實在太像恐怖片了
You go first. Are you scared?
你先走啊，你怕了嗎？
No, it's always ladies first as per my grandpa's will.
不，我爺爺最後的遺言 要我凡事都女士優先
Whatever.
算了
Stop that!
別這樣
What is this?
這是什麼？
Hey, how far does it go?
話說，這到底會通到哪裡啊？
Wait, what is that sound?
等等，那是什麼聲音？
You stay here.
你別走
Did you do that, Izzy?
伊姬，是妳弄的嗎？
I sense strong demon powers ahead.
我感覺到前方有強大的妖氣
There is no need to endanger your friends.
沒必要讓你的朋友陷入危險
Thank you. Actually, I want to leave, too.
謝謝，但我也想回去
You're so naive, Hachi. I told you.
你太天真了，小八，我明明告訴過你
What happens to me will affect you, too. Did you forget that?
要是我怎麼了 你也會受到影響，你忘記了嗎？
To be honest, I still don't get it.
老實說 我還是不太懂那是什麼意思
Who's there?
是誰？
Hello.
你們好
Kouki Shikazono?
鹿園弘規？
Princess Izuna-imiki!
伊綱忌寸公主大人！
The one who destroys the world.
毀滅世界之人
You came to this world.
妳來到了陽界
Who is he?
這傢伙是什麼人？
He's a student here. He's been missing.
他是我們大學的學生，他失蹤了
Hey, everyone is worried about you.
聽我說，大家都很擔心你
For the longest time,
長久以來
I've been trying to summon Ms. Izuna.
我一直在嘗試召喚伊綱大人
But why you?
但為什麼是你？
Are you a zombie now?
你該不會變成喪屍了吧？
I'm not a zombie!
我才不是喪屍！
I'm just a corpse!
我只是個活死人！
He's been brought back from death.
他是被人復生的活死人
You can't reason with him.
沒辦法跟他講道理
We'll look for the one controlling him.
我們要找出控制他的人
Cursed stones are in place now.
詛咒的石頭現在已經就位
You can't go through the shadows anymore.
妳已經不能穿越影子了
You and I
妳和我…
were supposed to be together...
本來應該在一起的
-Let's hurry on. -Yes.
–我們快點前進吧 –好
So it's you.
果然是你
I'll beat you out of this place!
我要把妳趕出這裡
You're the one that's going to die!
該消失的人是你
So you're the fool that had sex with her.
所以你就是那個和她交媾的笨蛋
-That's not helping! -I'm sorry!
–你這樣根本沒幫上忙！ –對不起
I hold no personal grudge.
我跟你沒有個人恩怨
Why, you...
妳這傢伙…
This place has a barrier and we can't escape into the shadow.
這裡設下了結界，沒辦法遁入影子
-We'll retreat. -Yes.
–先暫時撤退吧 –好
Why, you...
混帳東西…
This way!
走這邊！
Where is this? A cemetery?
這是哪裡？墓地嗎？
Izzy!
伊姬！
Here you go.
給妳
Who was that?
那個人到底是誰？
Tenkai.
他叫天迴
He broke the rules of life and became a living corpse.
他打破生命的法則，成了一個活死人
He used to be a samurai who served the Five Spears.
他曾經是效忠五矛會的武士
I assume he's serving them again.
恐怕他又在為他們效命了吧
Do you mean he died and came back to life again?
妳說他是活死人 意思是他死過一次又復活了？
Seriously? Our situation got worse!
不會吧？情況越來越糟糕了
The Five Spears will pursue me until they kill me.
五矛會的人 應該會持續追查我，直到殺了我為止
So it's either you kill them or they kill you?
所以，要麼妳殺死他們 不然他們就會殺了妳？
That's not all.
不只是這樣
They know about our bond now.
他們現在知道我們之間的關聯了
When one of the pair dies, the other one dies as well.
締結羈絆的兩人 只要一人死去，另一個人也會死
Is that why he attacked me?
所以他才會攻擊我嗎？
I should have predicted this.
我早該想到這一點的
Your friends were almost killed, too.
你的朋友也差點被殺了
But you let Tanuki and Hikari escape before that happened.
可是，妳已經先讓狸貓和小光逃走了
Izzy, I just learned this recently,
伊姬，我最近才學到一件事
but the world is a lot more complicated than I thought.
世界遠比我想像的複雜
Everything can be changed.
或許一切都可以改變
I'll help you look for the Dragon's Magatama.
我來幫妳尋找龍勾玉吧
You are just too soft.
你果然還是太天真了
But I'll think of a way
但我會想辦法
so you don't have to kill anybody anymore.
讓妳不必再殺人
I'll come up with something.
我一定會想出辦法的
What's at this temple?
這座寺廟裡面有什麼嗎？
Just to make sure.
只是來確認一下
Cemeteries are exciting at night. Something might appear.
晚上的墓地感覺會鬧鬼，好興奮喔
Something appeared!
真的出現了
Captain! Wait for me!
警部！等我一下！
What is it?
怎麼了嗎？
I'm late.
我來晚了
Sakon, you must have a good reason to be late.
居然遲到，你也變大牌了嘛，左近
The police are investigating that incident.
警方在調查上次的事件
They're on to me. It took me awhile to lose their trail.
他們在跟蹤我 我花了一些時間才甩掉他們
Enough with your excuses. Get started.
別再找藉口了，快點開始吧
That Yokai is still acting as she pleases.
那個妖怪依然逍遙在外
But there's no need to worry.
但無需擔心
Our emissary, Tenkai, is on the move.
我們的侍從天迴正在採取行動
"Our"?
“我們的”？
Sakon, you're our emissary, too.
左近，你也是我們的侍從
My apologies.
請原諒我的無禮
She can come to my house if she wants.
她想要的話就來我家吧
I'll teach that Yokai woman a lesson!
我會讓那個女妖怪知道厲害
Sakon, what if Tenkai fails?
左近先生，要是天迴失敗了怎麼辦？
First of all, who summoned a Yokai?
話說回來，到底是誰召喚了妖怪？
The stolen forbidden book hasn't been found yet.
被偷的禁書還沒找到
We are diligently searching for it.
我們正在努力尋找
That's why Hayato died.
隼人就是因此喪命的
That's why I opposed it.
所以我才反對
But you can't serve as a Guardian with your body.
但你現在的身體已經當不了守護者
Hayato was my only son.
隼人是我唯一的兒子
Everyone, now is the time to unite.
各位，現在該是我們團結的時候
For several thousand years, our five families
幾千年來，我們五個家族
transformed barbaric Yokai magic
將野蠻的妖怪魔法
into useful forms to make a fortune.
轉化為有益的形式，藉此致富
We won't lose it.
我們不能失去這一切
Isn't that right, Ninomiya?
是吧，二之宮？
Yes, you're exactly right, chairperson.
是的，會長說得一點也沒錯